Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art buildings and grounds records, 1870-2007 COR0007.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Administrative records, Series 13
  - General administrative files, Series 13 subseries 3
    - Art School Space 15th & M St. NW, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Art School Committee List, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Attendence Reports, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Audit File, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Budget Information- Review Income & Expenses, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Budget File, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Business Land, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Capitol Campaign, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Contract Information, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Cooper's & Lybrand, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Corcoran Shop Sales, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Cultural Alliance, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Dun & Bradstreet, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Emergency Telephone Call Procedure, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Ethics Policy-Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Exhibition Schedule, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Friends of Corcoran, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Grant/Gifts, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Group Admissions, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - In-House Calendar of Events, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Insurance Committee File, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Huntington T. Block Policies General Information, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Investment & Finance Committee, 1988; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Legal Issures, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Materials- Staff Mtg, 1989 February 24; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Memorandums Security/Operations, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Memorandums, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - National Building Museum/Pension Building- Art School, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - PR- Press Releases, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Pre-Event Worksheets, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Search Committee, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Shop Sales Odyssey Exhibition, 1988-1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Tax Exempt Status Requests, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Trustees Luncheons- Invoices, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Weekly Attendance Reports, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Women's Committee List, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Women's Committee, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Yaffe Bulletin, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Minutes & Correspondence for Committees & Meetings, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Art School Committee Meeting, 1989; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Art School Self Study Planning & Finance Comte, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Audit Committee Meeting, 1989 January 27; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Investment & Finanace Comm. Mtg, 1988 June 8; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - The Corcoran Gallery of Art Fiscal Year Budget Papers, 1988 June 8; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Investment & Finance Comm. Mtg, 1988 November 8; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Investment & Finance Comte Mtg., 1989 January 23; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Final Budget Materials Budgets to Depts; Budget to Bd., undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Investmment & Finance Cmt. Mtg. (Budget Review), 1989 May 2; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Chronological File, 1991; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Chronological File, 1990 July 1-1990 December 31; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Chronological File, 1990 January 1-June 30; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Chronological Memoradum File, 1989 August 1-December 31; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Chronological Memoradum File, 1988 December-1989 July 31; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Coopers & Lybrnd Correspondence, 1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Fax File- Information Faxed, 1989-1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Memorandums Operations, 1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Memorandums Security Department, 1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Memorandums- Incoming, 1991; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Correspondences- Incoming, 1991; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Fax Information- Incoming, 1991; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Memorandums- Outgoing, 1991; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence- Outgoing, 1991; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Legal Correspondence, 1991; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Computer Information, 1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Legal Fees Purchase Orders, 1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - ADM. Purchase Orders, 1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - New York Avenue Bldg. Project, 1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Executive Committee, 1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Audit Committee, 1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Building & Grounds Committee, 1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Investment and Finance Committee, 1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Planning & Finance Self-Study Committee, circa 1989-1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Committee Assignments, 1989-1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Board of Directors, 1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Internat. Surplus Lines/D&O AAM NAT Program, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Johnson & Higgins/St. Pail Fire & Marine (Nat Rep Senat Cmte), 1991 November 12; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Insurance Purchase Orders, 1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Huntington T. Block General Correspondence, 1992; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Hartford Insurance General Correspondence, 1992; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Huntington T. Block Ins Memo Re: Issues to be Addressed, 1992; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Insurance/Package Proposals, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Audit Materials Mailed to New Board of Trustees, 1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Full Board Meeting, 1991 November 18; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1991 July 15; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Finance, and Audit Report Executive Committee Meeting, 1991 October 21; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1991 October 21; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Investment Managers Meeting, 1992 January 9; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Investment Mgrs. & Finance Meeting, 1992 April 9; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Handicapped, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - DHW (Domestic hot water and other plumbing), undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Surdna, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Mellon, 1979; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Architecture, Planning, & Design Grant Application, 1979 May 15; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Mellon Grant, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Proposal NEA- Renovation, Climate, Storage, Security, 1979; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - CAC Funding, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Personnel, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Annual Reports, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - IBM, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Grants- Prospective, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Development, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Climate Control NEA Proposal, 1981; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Kresge, 1981 November 18; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Climate Control Proposals, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Floors, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Building Permits, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - CAC- Kresge, 1981 February 12; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Budget, 1978-1980; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Purchases, 1980; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Maintenance, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Sprinkler System, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Audit, Correspondence, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Alcoholic Beverage, Correspondence, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Budget, Accounting, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Budget, Institution, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Budget, Operation, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Budget, Memoradum/Levy, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Contract, Maint/Cummins, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Budget, Fin/Adm Dept, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, R. Varmall, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Documenet/Industry Verfication/Dept Employment Services, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Events, Corcoran Ball, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Files, List, 1992; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Guide, Wash Post Advert., undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Law Offices, Correspondence, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Law Offices, Newsletters, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Notice, Bankrupt/Gareth, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Notice, Postal/Address, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Office Supplies, Acctg. Dept., undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Postage Reports, 1992; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Postage Reports, 1991; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Reference, Systems Eval., undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Reimbursements, Correspondence, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Reference, Gas Well Proceeds, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Reference, Women's Comm., undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Reports/Operating Rev/Exp, 1992 March 31; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Reports/Rev/Exp w/ Encumber, 1992 June 30; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Reports/Alcoholic Beverage, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Directors Office/Institutional Dues 01-08-00-4724, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Archives/Professional Training 01-12-00-5602, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - PERS/Staff Relations 11-00-5313, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Consulting Services 01-11-00-5108, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Software Services 01-11-00-5112, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Manuals 01-11-00-4722, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Dev/Chernikoff 20-71-5108, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Dev/Donor Cultivation 20-00-5316, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - Mus/Prepaid Expense 01-00-00-1710, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Mus/Suspense Account 01-00-00-2099, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Nonbudget/Contract Help 10-00-5203, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - Fin/Legal Fees 09-00-5104, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - Non-budget/Museum/Search Committee 01-00-00-4136, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - Royalties 01-00-00-3905, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - Acctg/Shipping & Handling 01-10-00-4204, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - Non-Budget/NY Avenue/Archive Expense 04-60-00-4740, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - NY Avenue/Legal 04-60-00-5104, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - C. Dudley Lect. Fund 36-00-00-5004, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - Inst/Mgmt Exp/Stein Roe & 08-00-00-7012, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - Fin/Benefits-Full 09-00-4106, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 47)
    - Fin/Stationary, Forms, & Supplies 09-00-4716, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 48)
    - Fin/Salaries 09-00-4102, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 49)
    - Fin/Subscriptions 09-00-4718, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 50)
    - Fin/Equipement-Office 09-00-4729, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 51)
    - Fin/Office Supplies 09-00-4732, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 52)
    - Fin/Mail Services Exclude Pstg 09-00-4734, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 53)
    - Fin/Personal "Computers" 09-00-4751, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 54)
    - Adm/Printing 01-09-00-5052, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 55)
    - Fin/Software Systems 09-00-5112, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 56)
    - Fin/PC Supplies 09-00-5114, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 57)
    - Inst/Mgmt Exp/Loomis Sayl. 07-00-00-7012, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 58)
    - Non-budget/Other Business Expense 09-00-5303, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 59)
    - Fin/Travel 09-00-5304, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 60)
    - Fin/Entertainment 09-00-5306, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 61)
    - Acctg/Supplemental Salaries 10-00-4134, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 62)
    - Acctg/Forms & Paper 10-00-4716, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 63)
    - Acctg/Subscriptions 10-00-4718, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 64)
    - Acctg/Technical Publications 10-00-4720, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 65)
    - Acctg/Refer Mat/Maunals 01-10-00-4722, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 66)
    - Acctg/Institutional Dues 10-00-4724, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 67)
    - Acctg/Equipment Office 01-10-00-4729, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 68)
    - Acctg/Office Supplies 10-00-4732, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 69)
    - Acctg/Mail Services 10-00-4734, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 70)
    - Acctg/Personal Computer 10-00-4751, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 71)
    - No-budget/Acctg/Printing Services 10-00-5016, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 72)
    - Acctg/Printing-Admin 10-00-5052, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 73)
    - Acctg/Audit 10-00-5102, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 74)
    - Acctg/Tax 10-00-5103, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 75)
    - Accounting/Support 01-10-00-5106, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 76)
    - Acctg/Maint Contracts New & DMCC 10-00-5113, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 77)
    - Non-budget/Acctg/PC Supplies 10-00-5114, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 78)
    - Acctg/Software Systems ADP 10-00-5112, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 79)
    - Personnel/Software Systems ADP 01-11-00-5112, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 80)
    - Acctg/Other Business Expense 10-00-5303, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 81)
    - Acctg/Travel 10-00-5304, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 82)
    - Acctg/Entertainment 10-00-5306, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 83)
    - Acctg/Staff Relations 10-00-5313, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 84)
    - Acctg/Professional Training 10-00-5802, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 85)
    - Building & Grounds Meeting Date Cancelled, 1992 March 19; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 86)
    - Building & Grounds Meeting Date, 1992 May 21; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 87)
    - Finance Meeting, 1992 April 30; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 88)
    - Finance Meeting, 1992 June 18; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 89)
    - Finance Meeting Date Cancelled, 1992 July 9; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 90)
    - Finance & Audit Meeting Date, 1992 March 12; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 91)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art Office Building Project Manual Volume 2, circa 1987-1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 38, Folders 1-2)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art Office Building Project Manual Volume 3, circa 1987-1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 38, Folders 3-4)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art Office Building Project Manual Volume 4, circa 1987-1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 38, Folders 5-6)
    - Addendum No. 1 for the Corcoran Gallery of Art Office Building, circa 1987-1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Addendum No. 2 for the Corcoran Gallery of Art Office Building, circa 1987-1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Amendments to the General Conditions of the Contract for Construction, 1987; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Amendments to the Standard Form of Agreement Between Owner and Contractor, 1987; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Hartford/Package Policy, 1990 April 10; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Hartford/Package Policy, 1989 April 10; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - St. Paul/Employee Benefit, 1988 September 1; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Home Insur. Co./Fine Arts Legal Liability, 1992 March 23; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Home Insur. Co./Fine Arts Legal Liability, 1991 March 23; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Hartford Steam/Boiler, 1993 March 27; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Life Insurance Co. of N. Am/Cigna Volunteer Accident, 1992 October 12; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Life Insurance Co. of N. Amer. Volunteer Accident, 1991 October 12; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Life Insurance Co. of N. Amer. Volunteer Accident, 1990 October 12; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Life Insurance Co. of N. Amer. Volunteer Accident, 1987 October 12; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Chubb/Federal Insurance Co. Directors & Officers Liab., 1992 November 7; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - CNA/Directors' & Officers' Friends of the Corcoran, 1991 November 7; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - CNA- Directors' & Officers' (Friends of the Corcoran) Policy, 1991 November 7; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Hartford/Work-Comp & EMP-Liab, 1993 April 10; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Hartford/Work-Comp & EMP-Liab, 1992 April 10; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Hartford/Work-Comp & EMP-Liab, 1991 April 10; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Hartford/Work-Comp & EMP-Liab, 1990 April 10; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Centennial/Workers' Comp., 1988 April 10; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Hartford Vault Liability Policy, 1993 June 23; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Hartford Insur/Vault Liab., 1992 June 23; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Hartford Insur/Vault Liab., 1991 June 23; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Hartford Insurance/Umbrella, 1993 April 10; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Hartford Ins/Umbrella, 1992 April 10; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Hartford Ins/Umbrella, 1991 April 10; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Hartford/Package Policy, 1992 April 10; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Hartford/Package Policy, 1991 April 10; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Budget Operations, 1992; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Admin/General Form W-9/Tax ID Certific Salomon Brothers Request, 1992; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Admin/General February Operating Rep., 1992; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Admin/General One-Time Pay, 1992; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Admin/General Contract Work/SOC SEC, 1992; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Admin/General Committee Meeting Dates, 1992; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Adm/Pers/Alphabetical List of Employees, 1992; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Finance/ A/P Procedures, 1992; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Financial/Board of Trustees Orientation, 1992; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Finance/New PO Procedures, 1992 January; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - Admin/General Draft/Financial Stmts, 1991; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Insurance Policy Information (Hunting T. Block), 1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Huntington T. Block Ins. Monthly Statements, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - CNA/Directors & Officers Application Only, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - CHUBB/Directors' & Officers' Application Only, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - Art School Alumni Exhibition Standard All Risk F/A Insur. FDIC Bldg/550 17th St, 1991 September; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 42)
    - Form "Erm-14" Nat'l Council on Compensation Insurance Re: Workers Compresation Policy, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 43)
    - Hartford Insurance Renewals Works Compensation, Gallery, & Umbrella Liability, 1991 April 1; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 44)
    - Huntington T. Block- War Risk, undated; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 45)
    - St. Paul/Employee Benefit #GL00608656 Exp 9/1/90, 1990 September 1; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 46)
    - Insurance/General Liability, 1991; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 47)
    - Insurance/Workman's Comp., 1991; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 48)
    - Financial/Budget, 1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 49)
    - Financial/Capital Campaign Budget, 1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 50)
    - Financial/Develop. Reports, 1990; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 51)
    - Finance/Chart of Accounts, 1990-1991; Series 13 subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 52)